## PATRICK LEWIS

1135 Barton Hills Dr. #149 Austin, TX 78704 512-656-0350 patrickblewis@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

UX/UI Developer with over 10 years experience creating web applications. I enjoy working collaboratively with a team to design, prototype, test and deliver products. Currently looking to join a fun team working on interesting projects where I can be a valuable contributor.

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

**HomeAway** Austin, TX

UX Developer at HomeAway

2015 - 2016

- Helped establish the new Design Technologist role within the UX Design team.
- Collaborated with designers and product managers to create testable prototypes.
- Participated in user testing to create new iterations based the results.
- Joined team responsible for developing the final product to help with creating the experience.

Austin, TX **HomeAway** 2011 - 2015

*UI Developer at HomeAway* 

- Lead UI developer on property management team for 3 years.
- Created property management dashboard with tools enabling the management of many properties at once.
- Created a javascript plugin to provide a i18n enabled feedback tab across all global brands
- Built early products primarily with backbone, handlebars, and an in-house 'thin-ui' java based system which allows decoupling of the UI and backend applications.
- Adopted React later to replace the UI stack.

## **BancVue Interactive**

Austin, TX

Senior Front-end Developer

2009 - 2011

- Created credit union web sites using html, css, Javascript and a content management system.
- Introduced the use of SASS and methods to ensure cross browser consistency.
- Improved the efficiency, quality and speed of sites created.
- Selected to work on special projects involving Javascript/css3 solutions to replace flash.

Sundry Studio Austin, TX

Designer & Front-end Developer

2005 – 2009

• Worked with clients and advertising agencies to design and develop search engine optimized websites that can easily be maintained through a content management system.

# **EDUCATION & EXPERIENCE**

- B.S. in Psychology Louisiana State University in 2000
- 4 years United States Marine Corps Squad Leader, TOW platoon 3<sup>rd</sup> Marine Division

## **SKILLS**

- Javascript along with React, Vuejs, and webpack
- css and pre / post processors
- semantic and accessible html5
- UX/UI best practices
- Currently playing with Vuejs Cordova apps